

MUHAMET HALITI

PROFILE

Senior Business Analyst offering over 10 years of experience providing technical support by utilizing an array of technology and software programs. I excel in translating business requirements into technical solutions; and I am fanatical about quality, usability and scalability. I have designed dozen of software solutions driving continuous improvement to processes, systems and work flows. I have strong written and verbal communications skills and I am always interested in a challenging technical career.

CONTACT



1308 Creosote Drive Fort Worth, TX 76177



612-810-7496



muhamet.haliti@me.com



www.muhamet-haliti.com

SKILLS

C# & VB NET

T-SQL, Toad, DB2

HTML & CSS

PHP/Javascript/JQuerv

Photoshop & Illustrator

MUHAMET HALITI

Formal Education

2010 - 2011 MBA

Emphasis in Finance Hamline University Minneapolis, MN

2004 - 2008 Bachelor of Science

Business Admin

Metropolitan State University Saint Paul, MN

Work experience

Sep 2016 Senior Business Analyst

Mr. Cooper

- Coordinate multiple project from development to production implementation.
- Provide solutions by utilizing research, analysis, SQL, and problem solving tools and techniques.
- $\bullet \quad \text{Implement and enhance data review process to find missing or invalid data, trends, anomalies}.$
- Serve as a business liaison for stakeholders and support personnel to coordinate multiple tasks.

 A saint with data analysis data manning Validation project accordinate multiple tasks.
- Assist with data analysis, data mapping, Validation, project oversight and other routine tasks.

 Study and graphysts existing department proceedings and propose shours as product to improve the propose of th
- Study and evaluate existing department procedures and propose changes as needed to improve
 overall efficiency and mitigate cost.

2012 - 2016 Interim Financial Analyst

Bank of America

- $\bullet \;\;$ Managed and maintained various SQL databases, jobs, procedures, and functions.
- Developed, tested, and deployed various business reports and productivity tools.
- Helped others grow their skillsets and improve the overall brand of our team.
- $\bullet \ \ Analyzed \ and \ mined \ data \ to \ provide \ reporting \ to \ aide \ with \ strategic \ decision \ making.$
- Subject matter expert on multiple systems and applications.

2011 - 2012 Financial Analyst

JP Morgan Chase

- Responsible for creating and reconciling various corporate accounts.
- Created and validated borrowers corporate advance fees.
- Created various process improvement tools.
- Ensure adherence to Compliance, Risk, Legal, and SOX rules.

Core Competencies

- Data Analytics
- SQL Development
- Quality Assurance
- Technical Support
- Systems Integration
- Web Development
- Logo Design
- Adobe Illustrator
- Microsoft Office
- Troubleshooting

What I'm doing!







Letters Programming HTML, CSS, Javascript Desktop Applications CSharp/VB.NET/SQL Web & Design PHP/Javascript/JQuery